http://cyberlawstudio.com/w/privacy-policy/

Contact
03.21.2020Julia Cheng invited by NAPO-LA to speak on Dynamex case, March
26, 2019.
Privacy Policy
Last updated: June 18, 2020
We recognize that your privacy is very important.
This privacy policy covers the policies of CyberlawStudio Group P.C. (“CyberlawStudio”) on the collection, use, and disclosure of your information, including any personally identifiable information or other data collected that could directly or indirectly identify you (“Personal Data”) when you access the CyberlawStudio website at www.cyberlawstudio.com   (the “Site”).
Each time you visit our Site, you consent to the collection, use and storage of the collected information as described in this Privacy Policy. Please read it carefully and contact us at esquire@cyberlawstudio.com  if you have any questions.
1. What information do we collect?
Inquiry Information:
When you e-mail us through the Site, you will provide us with your email address. You may also in your email, voluntarily provide us with the following Personal Data: names, physical addresses and phone numbers.
Cookies:
As of the date of this Privacy Policy, we do not use cookies. In the future, we may log information using “cookies.” Cookies are small data files stored on your hard drive by a website. We may use both session cookies (which expire once you close your web browser) and persistent cookies (which stay on your computer until you delete them) to provide you with a more personal and interactive experience on our Site. This type of information is collected to make the Site more useful to you and to tailor the experience with us to meet your special interests and needs.
2. How is collected information used?
We collect and process the Personal Data to respond to inquiries and fulfill our legal and professional obligations.
Legal Basis For Processing. When we process your information we will only do so where at least one of the following applies:
Provide our service to you: Most of the time, the reason we process your information is to perform the contract that you have with us. For example, if you email us through the Site to make an inquiry and provide Inquiry Information, we will use the Inquiry Information to respond to your inquiry.
Consent: From time to time, we may ask for your consent to use your information for certain specific reasons. You may withdraw your consent at any time by contacting us at the address provided at esquire@cyberlawstudio.com.
Legal Compliance: When it is necessary for us to use your information to comply with a legal obligations.
3. Is Information Collected by or Disclosed to Third Parties by using the Services?
We do not share, sell or rent to third parties your information except as described in this Privacy Policy.  Examples of instances in which we share your information are provided below:
Third party service providers. We, like many businesses, sometimes engage other companies to perform certain business-related functions on our behalf so that we can focus on our core business. Examples of these services include, but are not limited to, hosting service provider. We authorize them to use Personal Data only in connection data security and privacy standards.
Legal requirements. We may disclose your Personal Data if required to do so by law (including, without limitation responding to a subpoena or request from law enforcement, court or government agency or other public authorities) or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary (i) to comply with a legal obligation, (ii) to protect or defend our rights, interests or property or that of other customers or users, (iii) to act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of the Services or the public, or (iv) to protect against legal liability or potential fraud, as determined in our sole discretion.
Your consent. If we intend to use any of your Personal Data collected in any manner that is not specified herein, we will inform you of such anticipated use prior to or at the time at which such Personal Data is collected or we will obtain your consent subsequent to such collection but prior to such use. In short, we will honor the choices you make regarding your Personal Data and will inform you about any other intended uses of such information.
4. Linking to or from Third Party Platforms.
Users may follow CyberlawStudio on social media platforms as available. Users should click on the hyperlinks for each site to review the applicable privacy policies for more detail about information collected from these sites.
5. How Does CyberlawStudio Comply with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act?
Our Site is directed toward a general audience and are not directed at nor intended for use by children.  We do not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13 without parental consent. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with information without their consent, he or she should contact us at esquire@cyberlawstudio.com   We will delete such information from our files within a reasonable time.
6. What are my data protection rights under GDPR?
If you are located in certain countries, including those that fall under the scope of the GDPR, data protection laws give you rights with respect to your personal data, subject to any exemptions provided by the law, including the rights to:
Request access to your Personal Data;
Request correction or deletion of your Personal Data;
Object to our use and processing of your Personal Data;
Request that we limit our use and processing of your Personal Data; and
Request portability of your Personal Data.
You can usually access, correct, or delete your personal data by contacting us at  esquire@cyberlawstudio.com .  EU individuals also have the right to make a complaint to a government supervisory authority.
7. California Privacy Rights
Shine the Light
California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits visitors of our Site who are California residents to request certain information regarding and/or opt-out of our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. We do not disclose personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes.
California Consumer Privacy Act
California residents may request copies of the data collected about them in the past 12 months from businesses that sells, or shares for commercial purposes, alone or in combination, the personal information of 50,000 or more consumers, households, or devices. CyberlawStudio does not sell or share for commercial purposes, any personal information.
8. Data Transfers
Our Site is hosted by Aabaco Small Business LLC (operating as Yahoo! Small Business and a member of the Verizon group of companies, “YSB”).  YSB delivers an industry-leading network of state-of-the-art data centers located around the world. Like CyberlawStudio, helping to protect the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of customer data is of the utmost importance to YSB, as is maintaining customer trust and confidence. YSB has safeguards in place in accordance with applicable law to ensure that your personal data will, at all times and in all locations, be adequately protected to the standards required by applicable EEA Data Protection laws.  For more details of YSB’s privacy and security processes, please visit https://smallbusiness.yahoo.com/privacy-notice. By using the service, you consent to your personal information being transferred to our servers as set out in this policy.
9. How long does CyberlawStudio retain information collected?
We follow generally accepted standards to store and protect the Personal Data we collect, both during transmission and once received and stored, including utilization of encryption where appropriate.  We retain Personal Data only for as long as necessary to provide the services you have requested and thereafter for a variety of legitimate legal or business purposes. These might include retention periods (i) mandated by law, contract or similar obligations applicable to our business operations; (ii) for preserving, resolving, defending or enforcing our legal/contractual rights; or (iii) needed to maintain adequate and accurate business and financial records.  If you have any questions about the security or retention of your Personal Data, you can contact us at esquire@cyberlawstudio.com.
10. What is CyberlawStudio’s Security Policy?
We have implemented reasonable administrative, technical and physical security measures to protect your personal information against unauthorized access, destruction or alteration. For example, we limit access to this information to authorized employees and contractors who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services. However, although we endeavor to provide reasonable security for information we process and maintain, no security system can ever by 100% secure.
11. How Does CyberlawStudio Respond to “Do Not Track” Signals?
“Do Not Track” is a feature enabled on some browsers that sends a signal to request that a web application disable its tracking or cross-site user tracking. At present, CyberlawStudio does not respond to or alter its practices when a Do Not Track signal is received.
12. How Will I Be Notified of Changes to Your Privacy Policy?
If CyberlawStudio makes material changes to its Privacy Policy, it will notify you by: (i) changing the Last Updated Date at the top of the Privacy Policy, and/or (ii) adding a statement to the Site.
13. Contact Us
If you have any questions regarding privacy while using our Services, or have questions about our practices, please contact us via email at esquire@cyberlawstudio.com.
Last updated: June 18, 2020
©2020 CyberlawStudio Group P.C.
